A Guide to the Diplomas Collection
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Diplomas Collection ca.1830-ca.1970
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Multiple numbers
This collection consists of ca.1000 diplomas and certificates (7 oversize boxes), chiefly from the University of Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Acquired through gift and purchase.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of ca.1000 diplomas and certificates, chiefly from the University of Virginia.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by degree recipient's surname and is subarranged in reverse chronological order.
Contents List
- Adkisson,Joshua S. 1900 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Geology
- Adkisson, Joshua S. 1900 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, English Language
- Alden, Harold L. 1915 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mathematics
- Ambler, Mason G. 1899 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Law
- Ambler, Mason G. 1899 (Box 1)
- Anderson, Archer 1856 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Ancient Languages
- Anderson, Archer 1855 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Ancient Languages
- Anderson, Archer 1856 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Pure Mathematics
- Anderson, Archer 1856 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Moral Philosophy
- Anderson, Archer 1856 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Chemistry
- Archer, Carthon 1843 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Latin Language and Literature
- Archer, Carthon 1843 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, French and Spanish Language and Literature
- Archer, Carthon 1843 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Ancient Languages
- Astrop, Robert C. 1913 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, American Literature
- Atkisson, George H. 1907 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Economics
- Ayers, Irvin W. 1902 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, English Literature
- Ayers, Irvin W., 1902 (Box 1)
- Ayers, Irvin W. 1902 (Box 1)
- Baker, Charles W. 1909 (Box 1)
  National Geographic Society, Membership certificate
- Baker, Charles W. 1910 (Box 1)
  National Conservation Association, Membership certificate
- Baker, Charles W. 1878 (Box 1)
  State of Vermont, Certificate
- Baker, Charles W. 1886 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Civil Engineer, Civil Engineering
- Baker, Edward M. 1915 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Education
- Baker, Morton W. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Greek
- Baker, Morton W. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Chemistry
- Baker, Morton W. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A., History
- Baker, Morton W. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Latin
- Baker, Morton W. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A., French
- Baker, Charles W. 1893 (Box 1)
  American Society of Mechanical Engineers, Certificate
- Baldwin, James H. 1899 (Box 1)
- Baldwin, James H. 1899 (Box 1)
- Banister, Madison L. 1913 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Biblical Literature
- Barbour, John L. 1848 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Spanish Language and Literature\
- Barringer, Rufus H. 1904 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Chemistry (Analytical)
- Barringer, Rufus H. 1900 (Box 1)
- Battle, John S., Jr. 1940 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, B.A.
- Battle, John S., Jr. 1946 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, B.L., Law
- Beale, Robert C. 1900 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, German
- Beale, Robert C. 1900 (Box 1)
- Beale, Robert C. 1901 (Box 1)
- Beale, Robert C. 1901 (Box 1)
- Beale, Robert C. 1901 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Latin
- Beale, Robert C. 1901 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Greek
- Beatty, J. Frederick 1899 (Box 1)
- Beatty, J. Frederick 1899 (Box 1)
- Bell, H. M. 1915 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Chemistry (Industrial)
- Berger, Percy M. 1905 (Box 1)
- Berkeley, Francis Lewis, Jr. 1934 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, B.S.
- Berkeley, Francis Lewis, Jr. 1940 (Box 1)
- Berry, R. C. 1915 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Chemistry (Analytical and Industrial)
- Betts, Alton W. 1907 (Box 1)
- Bickers, William C. 1901 (Box 1)
- Bickers, William C. 1901 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, History
- Bickers, William C. 1901 (Box 1)
- Birkhead, E. F., Jr. 1909 (Box 1)
- Bitting, Samuel T. 1913 (Box 1)
- Blair, Donald McK. 1905 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Natural Philosophy
- Blair, Donald McK. 1904 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Natural History and Geology
- Blair, Donald McK. 1904 (Box 1)
- Bolling, Albert S. 1900 (Box 1)
- Bolling, Albert S. 1900 (Box 1)
- Bomar, John E. 1913 (Box 1)
- Bonn, Carl P. 1906 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Philosophy
- Bonn, Carl P. 1905 (Box 1)
- Boone, William E. 1913 (Box 1)
- Bowcock, J. McCue 1899 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Pathology and Surgical Diseases
- Bradley, Mina 1887 (Box 1)
  Kent High School, Diploma
- Brent, Chester H. 1915 (Box 1)
- Brent, Chester H. 1915 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, English and American Literature
- Brent, Chester H. 1913 (Box 1)
- Brent, Chester H. 1902 (Box 1)
- Bright, James C. 1895 (Box 1)
- Brockenbrough, John N. 1843 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.D., Medicine
- Brockenbrough, John N. 1835 (Box 1)
- Brown, J. Thompson, Jr. 1907 (Box 1)
- Brown, William G. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, French
- Brown, A. Gordon 1899 (Box 1)
- Burton, George L. 1889 (Box 1)
- Burton, George L. 1889 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mathematics (Pure)
- Burton, George L. 1890 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Logic
- Burton, George L. 1890 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Chemistry (General)
- Burton, George L. 1890 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Graduate, Greek
- Butler, Edwin R. 1911 (Box 1)
- Butzner, John D. 1901 (Box 1)
- Butzner, John D. 1901 (Box 1)
- Byrd, T. B. 1909 (Box 1)
- Byrd, A. M. 1896 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Physiology
- Byrd, A. M. 1896 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Anatomy
- Cabell, James L. 1882 (Box 1)
  American Medicine Academy, Certificate
- Cabell, James L. 1881 (Box 1)
  Société Royale de Médecin Publique de Belgique, Certificate
- Cabell, James L. 1836 (Box 1)
  Trustees of the Poor, Baltimore City and County, Certificate of Residency
- Cabell, James L. 1834 (Box 1)
  Academy of Maryland, M.D., Medicine
- Cabell, James L. 1833 (Box 1)
- Cabell, James L. 1833 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, M.A.
- Cabell, James L. 1833 (Box 1)
- Cabell, James L. 1832 (Box 1)
- Cabell, James L. 1832 (Box 1)
- Cabell, James L. 1831 (Box 1)
- Caldwell, H. M. 1909 (Box 1)
- Calisch, Edward N. 1902 (Box 1)
- Camp, John M. 1907 (Box 1)
- Camp, Robert G. 1906 (Box 1)
- Camp, Robert G. 1905 (Box 1)
- Campbell, Charles 1900 (Box 1)
- Carney, Alonzo B. 1899 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1907 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1907 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, Latin
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1907 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1906 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, Chemistry
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1906 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, English Literature
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1906, Charlottesville High School, Diploma, German (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1906 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1905 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, Geometry
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1905 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, Deportment
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1905 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, Government
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1905 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1905 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, German
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1904 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1904 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1904 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1904 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1904 (Box 1)
- Carver, Alphonso P. 1901 (Box 1)
  Charlottesville High School, Diploma, English grammar
- Carver, Thomas P. 1877 (Box 1)
  Ridge Street Academy, Diploma, Arithmetic
- Carver, Thomas P. 1877 (Box 1)
  Ridge Street Academy, Diploma, English grammar
- Chamberlayne, Churchill G. 1900 (Box 1)
- Chamberlayne, Churchill G. 1900 (Box 1)
- Chamberlayne, Churchill G. 1900 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Moral Philosophy (Logic and Psychology)
- Chamberlayne, Churchill G. 1900 (Box 1)
- Chamberlayne, Lewis P. 1902 (Box 1)
- Chamberlayne, Lewis P. 1902 (Box 1)
- Chamberlayne, J. Hampden 1901 (Box 1)
- Chamberlayne, J. Hampden 1900 (Box 1)
- Chumbley, R. E. Lee 1902 (Box 1)
- Church, Herman 1913 (Box 1)
- Claiborne, John H. 1850 (Box 1)
  Pennsylvania Hospital, Certificate of Residency, Medicine
- Claiborne, John H. 1850 (Box 1)
  Jefferson College, M.D., Medicine
- Clark, Abraham L. 1845 (Box 1)
- Clark, Thomas G. 1913 (Box 1)
- Clarke, John A. 1906 (Box 1)
- Clarke, John A. 1905 (Box 1)
- Clarke, John A. 1905 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Romance Languages (Italian)
- Cleborne, Alan B. 1899 (Box 1)
- Cline, J. Henry 1913 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Economic Geology
- Cocke, M. Estes 1900 (Box 1)
- Cocke, M. Estes 1900 (Box 1)
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1899 (Box 1)
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1899 (Box 1)
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1899 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Medicine
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1899 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Regional Anatomy
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1899 (Box 1)
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1898 (Box 1)
- Cocke, Norborne P. 1898 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Biology
- Coggin, W. B. 1909 (Box 1)
- Coggin, W. B. 1909 (Box 1)
- Coleman, Algernon 1901 (Box 1)
- Coleman, Algernon 1900 (Box 1)
- Connor, William W. 1899 (Box 1)
- Cook, Roy S. 1913 (Box 1)
- Cowardin, Harry A. 1915 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Mechanical Engineer, Mechanical Engineering
- Cox, Hardin A. 1895 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Law
- Crawford, George G. 1899 (Box 1)
- Crawford, Angus McD. 1902 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Romance Languages
- Crawford, Angus McD. 1901 (Box 1)
- Crimmins, Martin L. 1897 (Box 1)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Operative Surgery
- Croft, George W. 1888 (Box 1)
  Dunsmore's Business College, Certificate
- Crumbliss, Raleigh 1907 (Box 1)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, German Language and Literature
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Modern Languages
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Mathematics
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Natural Philosophy
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Moral Philosophy
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1881 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Literature
- Dabney, Richard H. 1880 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, History, Literature and Rhetoric
- Dabney, Richard H. 1880 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, French Language and Literature
- Dabney, Richard H. 1880 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Richard H. 1879 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Greek Language and Literature
- Dabney, Richard H. 1879 (Box 2)
- Dabney, Virginius 1895 (Box 2)
- Dancy, Frank B., Jr. 1915 (Box 2)
- Dargan, E. Preston 1901 (Box 2)
- Dargan, E. Preston 1900 (Box 2)
- Davidson, George D. 1905 (Box 2)
- Davidson, Clayton A. 1913 (Box 2)
- Davis, Gideon O. 1904 (Box 2)
- Demaine, Ernest M. 1906 (Box 2)
- Dey, William M. 1902 (Box 2)
- Dilworth, R. B. 1902 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mathematics (Applied)
- Dinwiddie, William 1854 (Box 2)
- Dinwiddie, William 1854 (Box 2)
- Dinwiddie, William 1854 (Box 2)
- Dinwiddie, William 1854 (Box 2)
- Dinwiddie, William 1854 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Chemisty
- Dinwiddie, William 1854 (Box 2)
- Dinwiddie, Edgar E. 1895 (Box 2)
- Dobie, Armistead M. 1902 (Box 2)
- Dobie, Armistead M. 1902 (Box 2)
- Dobie, Armistead M. 1902 (Box 2)
- Dobie, Armistead M. 1900 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Moral Philosophy (Logic and Philosophy)
- Donelson, Lewis R. 1904 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Romance Languages and Literature
- Donelson, Lewis R. 1900 (Box 2)
- Downing, John P. 1879 (Box 2)
- Drewry, Patrick H. 1899 (Box 2)
- Drumright, Ernest B. 1899 (Box 2)
- Dunlop, James N. 1900 (Box 2)
- Dunlop, James N. 1900 (Box 2)
- Eastman, J. S. 1909 (Box 2)
- Ebbert, Arthur, Jr. 1946 (Box 2)
- Ebbert, Arthur, Jr. 1944 (Box 2)
- Edmondson, Samuel W. 1905 (Box 2)
- Edmondson, Samuel W. 1905 (Box 2)
- Edmondson, Samuel W. 1905 (Box 2)
- Edmondson, Samuel W. 1904 (Box 2)
- Edmondson, John H. 1900 (Box 2)
- Edwards, John G. 1916 (Box 2)
- Edwards, Preston H. 1900 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Botany
- Eichelberger, Charles P. 1895 (Box 2)
- Eichelberger, Edward C. 1915 (Box 2)
- Everett, Norman Douglas 1966 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.S., Commerce
- Ewell, Jessie, Jr. 1909 (Box 2)
- Farish, Robert E. 1905 (Box 2)
- Faulkner, William H. 1902 (Box 2)
- Faulkner, Charles J. 1901 (Box 2)
- Faulkner, Charles J. 1901 (Box 2)
- Ferrel, Harry E. 1897 (Box 2)
- Fishburne, George P. 1901 (Box 2)
- Fitch, Ferris H. 1913 (Box 2)
- Fleet, William A. 1902 (Box 2)
- Fleet, William A. 1901 (Box 2)
- Flippin, J. Carroll 1900 (Box 2)
- Flory, John S. 1905 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Teutonic and English Language
- Foshee, Mason 1896 (Box 2)
- Foster, James W. 1913 (Box 2)
- Foster, James W. 1913 (Box 2)
- Foster, James W. 1913 (Box 2)
- Fretwell, William E. 1906 (Box 2)
- Furcron, Aurelius Sydney 1923 (Box 2)
- Furcron, Aurelius Sydney 1923 (Box 2)
- Gaither, Roscoe B. 1915 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Spanish
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., General Literature
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1879 (Box 2)
- Garnett, Jennings W. 1878 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Modern Languages
- Garnett, James B. 1913 (Box 2)
- Garnett, James B. 1913 (Box 2)
- Gaskins, John D. 1899 (Box 2)
- Gaver, Floyd W. 1905 (Box 2)
- Gaver, Floyd W. 1905 (Box 2)
- Gay, S. R. 1913 (Box 2)
- Geiger, Victor 1915 (Box 2)
- Gibbens, Robert G. 1889 (Box 2)
- Gibbs, R. S. 1915 (Box 2)
- Gillespie, David C. 1900 (Box 2)
- Gillespie, David C. 1900 (Box 2)
- Gilmer, John C. 1899 (Box 2)
- Gish, Beverly A. 1913 (Box 2)
- Givens, J. W. 1913 (Box 2)
- Givens, C. B. 1909 (Box 2)
- Givens, Elmer B. 1911 (Box 2)
- Goodrich, Edward 1915 (Box 2)
- Goodrich, Edward 1913 (Box 2)
- Gordon, John B. 1877 (Box 2)
- Gordon, John B. 1877 (Box 2)
- Gordon, John B. 1876 (Box 2)
- Gordon, John B. 1876 (Box 2)
- Gordon, John B. 1876 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency
- Gordon, John B. 1876 (Box 2)
- Gordon, John B. 1875 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mathematics (Pure) Mineralogy and Geology
- Grandy, Cyrus W. 1900 (Box 2)
- Grandy, William 1896 (Box 2)
- Grant, Benjamin E. 1915 (Box 2)
- Grattan, George G., Jr. 1899 (Box 2)
- Gray, Norborne R. 1908 (Box 2)
- Gray, Norborne R. 1908 (Box 2)
- Gray, William S. 1904 (Box 2)
- Green, Jesse H. 1913 (Box 2)
- Gretter, John H. 1828 (Box 2)
- Griggs, William G. 1895 (Box 2)
- Grove, George H. 1915 (Box 2)
- Hale, Oron J. 1958 (Box 2)
  Hampden-Sydney College, Litt.D., Honorary
- Hall, Samuel O. 1900 (Box 2)
- Hancher, Alfred M. 1905 (Box 2)
- Hanger, Franklin M., Jr. 1915 (Box 2)
- Hardaway, Horace 1886 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Geology
- Hardaway, Horace 1885 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mathematics, Applied
- Hardaway, Horace 1884 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Physics
- Hardaway, Horace 1882 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Mineralogy
- Harper, Ernest B. 1915 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Philosophy and Social Psychology
- Harris, Jerry M. 1858 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1858 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Graduate, Mathematics (Pure)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1859 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1859 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Ancient Languages
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Modern Languages
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Mathematics
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Natural Philosophy
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Chemistry
- Harris, Jerry M. 1860 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Moral Philosophy
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Greek
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harris, Jerry M. 1861 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Frederick N. 1911 (Box 2)
- Harrison, L. Carter 1902 (Box 2)
- Harrison, L. Carter 1902 (Box 2)
- Harrison, L. Carter 1900 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1879 (Box 2)
  State of New York, Certificate, Law
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1870 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1869 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Literature and Rhetoric
- Harrison, Robert L. 1869 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1869 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1869 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Political Economy
- Harrison, Robert L. 1868 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1868 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Graduate, Moral Philosophy
- Harrison, Robert L. 1867 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Robert L. 1867 (Box 2)
- Harvey, Ben 1907 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Chemistry (Analytical and Agricultural)
- Harvey, Ben 1907 (Box 2)
- Hastings, Thomas H.i 1899 (Box 2)
- Hay, James H., Jr. 1902 (Box 2)
- Hay, James H., Jr. 1902 (Box 2)
- Hayden, Charles 1836 (Box 2)
- Hayden, Charles 1836 (Box 2)
- Hayden, Charles 1836 (Box 2)
- Hickham, John 1844 (Box 2)
- Hightower, Robert Beall 1923 (Box 2)
  Jefferson Military College, Graduate
- Hill, William H. 1899 (Box 2)
- Hodges, Gentry 1906 (Box 2)
- Hodges, Gentry 1906 (Box 2)
- Hodges, Gentry 1906 (Box 2)
- Hoen, Harry H. 1913 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Petrology
- Hoffman, Richard M. 1902 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, English
- Holladay, Lewis 1896 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Biology (Histology and Bacteriology)
- Holladay, Waller 1872 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Mineralogy and Geology
- Holladay, Waller 1872 (Box 2)
- Holladay, Waller 872 (Box 2)
- Holladay, Waller 1861 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, French Language
- Holladay, Waller 1859 (Box 2)
- Holladay, Waller 1859 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mathematics (Mixed)
- Holladay, Waller 1858 (Box 2)
- Holladay, Waller 1858 (Box 2)
- Holladay, Waller 1858 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Spanish Language and Literature
- Holliday, M.A. 1914 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Organic Chemistry
- Holliday, M.A. 1914 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Physical Chemistry
- Holliday, M.A. 1911 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Analytical Chemistry
- Holt, Robert P. 1900 (Box 2)
- Horner, Albert A., Jr. 1906 (Box 2)
- Hoxton, Llewellyn G. 1900 (Box 2)
- Hull, William C. 1900 (Box 2)
- Hullihen, Walter W. 1895 (Box 2)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Italian
- Hume, John E. N. 1906 (Box 2)
- Hurst, Ira 1901 (Box 2)
- Jenkins, Charles E. 1913 (Box 3)
- Jerdone, Walter P. 1856 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Anglo Saxon
- Jerdone, Walter P. 1856 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Belles lettres
- Johns, Albert E. 1913 (Box 3)
- Johnson, Herman P. 1915 (Box 3)
- Johnson, Wills 1905 (Box 3)
- Johnston, Forney 1899 (Box 3)
- Johnston, Forney 1899 (Box 3)
- Johnstone, Albert S. 1906 (Box 3)
- Johnstone, Albert S. 1906 (Box 3)
- Jones, W. Barham 1907 (Box 3)
- Jones, W. Barham 1907 (Box 3)
- Jones, Lawrence C. 1915 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Romance Languages (French)
- Jones, Lawrence C. 1915 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Zoology
- Kaufman, Isadore 1900 (Box 3)
- Kaufman, Isadore 1900 (Box 3)
- Kean, William G. 1899 (Box 3)
- Kern, Francis A. 1905 (Box 3)
- Kinsolving, Wythe L. 1902 (Box 3)
- Kinsolving, Wythe L. 1902 (Box 3)
- Kirtley, James A. 1900 (Box 3)
- Kirtley, James A. 1900 (Box 3)
- Knight, L. M. S. 1911 (Box 3)
- Laforge, John 1967 (Box 3)
- Lake, T. Rosser 1902 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Teutonic Language and German
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Ancient Language and Literature
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1851 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1850 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1850 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1849 (Box 3)
- Latané, James A. 1849 (Box 3)
- Latané, Henry W. 1878 (Box 3)
- Latané, Henry W. 1878 (Box 3)
- Leach, Hugh 1915 (Box 3)
- Leach, Sydney 1896 (Box 3)
- Lear, Josie J. 1900 (Box 3)
- Leebrich, Robert G. 1913 (Box 3)
- Leigh, William 1902 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Teutonic Language
- Leigh, William 1902 (Box 3)
- Liggett, Winfield, Jr. 1900 (Box 3)
- Lunger, Henry J. 1913 (Box 3)
- Lyman, George 1899 (Box 3)
- MacCrae, Charles E. 1906 (Box 3)
- Mackall, William W. 1915 (Box 3)
- Madison, John P. 1902 (Box 3)
- Madison, John P. 1902 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Teutonic Language and English
- Madison, John P. 1902 (Box 3)
- Madison, John P. 1901 (Box 3)
- Maloney, William T. 1915 (Box 3)
- Manly, Albert B. 1905 (Box 3)
- Martin, Albert T. 1899 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Psychology
- Mason, H. Norton 1900 (Box 3)
- Mason, Randolph F. 1900 (Box 3)
- Massie, Robert K., Jr. 1913 (Box 3)
- Massie, Welford J. 1915 (Box 3)
- McCaleb, Frank L. 1895 (Box 3)
- McCallie, Henry D. 1904 (Box 3)
- McCartney, Thomas B. 1902 (Box 3)
- McCartney, Thomas B. 1902 (Box 3)
- McConnell, John P. 1901 (Box 3)
- McConnell, John P. 1901 (Box 3)
- McCranie, Marion A. 1899 (Box 3)
- McCue, Aurelia 1884 (Box 3)
  Virginia Female Institute, Diploma
- McCue, Aurelia 1884 (Box 3)
- McCue, Aurelia 1883 (Box 3)
- McCue, Aurelia 1883 (Box 3)
- McCue, John H. 1844 (Box 3)
- McCue, John H. 1843 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Washington Literary Society, Certificate
- McCue, John H. 1843 (Box 3)
- McCue, John H. 1843 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Natural Philosophy
- McCue, John H. 1843 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Moral Philosophy
- McCue, John H. n.d. (Box 3)
  Washington College, Certificate
- McCue, W. T. 1873 (Box 3)